[Music]
I just don't take movies that seriously
you know I mean if I did I'd believe
that every time I got on a mother plane
there'd be some mother
snakes which I do but that serves me
right for flying
spirit I thought it was cool that it did
show what it's like to come home from
war but you know like the love story was
like the female lead in it was just kind
of one-dimensional she just it kep was
the same scene over and over again with
her being like don't go to war don't go
to war don't go to war and it's like
this is the best shooter in the
world he's got to go to war right she
was like a broken Roomba just banging
against the same wall I know as a sniper
do you think Lee Harvey Oswell did it I
don't think he was by
himself
yeah there's no way I'm giving a sniper
weak te
easiest question ever we're all familiar
with the term first world problem right
it's when Rich Americans complain about
something that people in other parts of
the world might consider a byproduct of
luxury you know like when I have to turn
on the subtitles on Netflix because I'm
eating Doritos too loudly right you know
what I'm talking about yeah you want to
do what you can to help your kid but as
a black man in America I get a little
nervous when the government starts
poking me with needles you know
absolutely I'm saying and if you guys
remember the sky experiment you know
they told them they were working on
black on Bad Blood and they were giving
them syphilis so you know as a brother
I'm like what but you don't think your
kids are going to get Sy right you think
Tupac's still alive
Tupac if you look on I'm just saying if
you look if you look on his last album
he had the new Jordans on
true what again he's still
recording I think Mike it's all the
doctor Coke brothers you're really
making it difficult for me to boycott
you all right they can't possibly make
anything else that's an integral part of
my everyday life
Lyra the world's most comfortable
fabric okay we've got to figure this out
because nobody's taking my
Lyra I think there's always this talk
the illuminati people were controlling
the no it's two old white dudes and
their
brothers you can see them
we got they're not they're not
underground they're near Palm Springs
man you both get offered a gig opening
for the Coke brothers all
right and it pays a lot of money and
don't even try to tell me you're not
going to do it cuz every comic has a
price all right so I know you're going
to do it yes I'm just going to throw out
number you have to finish have to finish
that okay okay uh $1,000
no, no 10,000 no 100,000 you're thinking
about I'm thinking about 10 yeah you
think let me show you what an athlete
keeping it 100 looks like well I'm the
best corner of the game when you try me
with a sorry receiver like crab tree
that's the result you going to get don't
you ever talk about me see
see that that's 100 right I mean do you
know how scared America was for that
white woman oh my God is faking an
orgasm keeping it 70 hello or is it
lying well
why am I asking you it's keeping it
first of all I don't know what you're
talking
about but second of all I'd say it's
keeping it 70 it depends though if
you're not enjoying the sex at all and
you're faking it that's your Mar
lynching at that point all you have to
do is spend a month with Donald
Sterling hold on okay at his summer
house okay and he he never calls you
sherro okay oh fine the only ref first
use that's my right over
there hey America follow the nightly
show with Larry Wilmore on Twitter but
don't follow me home I want followers
but I don't want followers that's
stalking